mirc.com 2013-03-13

# mIRC: Privacy Policy

Welcome to mIRC. We want you to know that we respect your privacy and value your trust. We have written this privacy policy to let you know about the personal information, if any, that we collect about you when you use the mIRC website or the mIRC software, and what we do with that information. 

## What information do we collect?

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that your browser stores on your computer on behalf of the website that you are visiting. This allows a website to remember details about your visit, such as your preferences or the pages you have visited, and to provide useful features based on those details. The mIRC website uses cookies in a number of places, such as on the Registration page while processing your order or in the Discussion Forums while you are browsing or creating posts. If adverts are being displayed on the website, they may also use cookies for similar reasons. 

## Log Files and IP Addresses

As with all websites, visits to the mIRC website are logged by IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of pages visited. We do not share this information with any other organizations. We may occasionally use it ourselves to monitor the status of the website however. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information although visitors should be aware that both static and dynamic IP addresses can be mapped back to your Internet Service Provider. 

## Email addresses

We collect your email address when you subscribe to the mIRC mailing list and when you create an account on the mIRC Discussion Forums. We also collect your email address when you register mIRC. 

In the case of the mailing list, your email address is used only for the purpose of emailing you when a new version of mIRC is released and for no other purpose. You can add or remove yourself from the mailing list at any time through the Mailing List page. 

In the case of the Discussion Forums, your email address is used only for the purpose of allowing you to use your Discussion Forums account and for no other purpose. You can request deletion of your account at any time by contacting us. 

In the case of when you register mIRC, your email address is used to email you with your mIRC registration information after you have registered mIRC and for no other purpose. You can request deletion of your mIRC registration information at any time by contacting us. 

In all of the above cases, we will not sell, share, or rent this information to any other organizations. 

## Personal details

When registering mIRC through one of our selected resellers, you will be asked to provide personal details when placing your order, such as name, postal address, email address, and credit card information. These personal details are used only for the purpose of fulfilling your order and for no other purpose. 

We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any other organizations. 

## Securing your information

We take every reasonable precaution, and have strict policies in place, to protect any information that we collect from you from unauthorized access, misuse, or loss. 

## Links to other sites

This website and the mIRC software contain links to other sites and IP Addresses. Please be aware that mIRC is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies only to the information collected by mIRC. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may occasionally need to update our privacy policy and if we do we will post any changes to the policy on our website so that you are always aware of how we use your information. If at any time we find that we need to use information in a manner different from the policy stated at the time the information was collected, we will notify users by email and/or by posting a notice on our website. 

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us.
